你怎么了 你从哪拿的喷漆
Whafs wrong with you? Where did you even get that?
强尼 你干嘛呀
Johnny, what are you doing?
这里是911 有什么事吗
9-1-1, what is your emergency?
喂 这里是911
Hello? 9-1-1.
您有紧急情况吗
Do you have an emergency?
先生 您能说话吗
Sir, can you speak?
假若您不能说话
If you can't speak,
请按电话上的任意键
press any button on your phone.
按一次表示有 按两次表示没有
Once for yesz twice for no.
您还在听吗
Are you still there?
先生 请您不要挂机
Sir, I want you to stay on the line
好吗 我会追踪您的位置
for me, okay? I'm gonna track your location.
您还在听我说话吗
Are you still with me?
喂
Hello?
您还在听吗
Are you still there?
好吧 彼得森大道129号
Okay. 129, Peterson Drive,
迈尔斯县停尸房
Miles County Morgue.
先生 您还在听我说话吗
Sir, are you still with me?
请您不要走动 保持冷静
Just sit tight and remain calm.
警察和医护人员正在赶来
Police and paramedics are on their way
女士 我理解
Ma'am, I understand.
但我不能给你提供信息
But I can't give you that information.
保险单上只有你丈夫的名字
Your husband's the only one listed on the policy.
操
Bitch!
不 女士 不是对您说
No, ma‘am, not you. Not you.
妈 有卷尺吗
Mom, don't we have a tape measure?
不知道
I don't know.
去看看微波炉旁边的抽屉
Check the drawer by the microwave.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am!
我理解 但总有一天
I understand that, but in the future,
你丈夫会公布这份保险单的
your husband's going to have to call the policy.
我只能告诉你它还有效
All I can tell you is that it's still active.
对
Yes.
出去等五分钟 找你弟弟去
Can you wait five minutes, and go get your brother, please?
对 女士
Yes, ma'am.
我的上司也只会跟你说
My manager is just gonna tell you
同样的话
the same thing.
所以 你想好
So, did you figure out
明天要如何打扮了吗
what youfre dressing up as tomorrow?
迈尔斯县的小丑
The Miles County clown.
- 别这样 - 为啥
-Don't do that, -Why not?
因为这样很没礼貌
Because that's beyond disrespectful.
你们在说什么
What are we talking about?
他想打扮成那个去年杀了九个人的小丑
He wants to dress up as a real guy who murdered nine people last year.
你知道这有多寒心吗
Do you have any idea how insensitive that is?
更不用说 令人作呕
Not to mention, sick.
- 哦 你不能这么做 - 只是一套衣服
-Oh, you're not doing that. -It's just a costume.
愿天保佑 要是他袭击了我们家的人
How would you feel if God forbid,
人们却都在庆祝他
he attacked someone in our family,
你会作何感想
and people celebrated him?
这就是你打算干的事
That's basically what you're doing.
你不会看到有人打扮成杰夫瑞·达莫
You don't see people dressing up as Jeffrey Dahmer
或者查尔斯·曼森
or Charles Manson.
我觉得你们太大惊小怪了
I think you're both overreacting.
是吗
Do you?
严格来说查尔斯·曼森从未杀过人
Charles Manson technically never killed anyone.
行了 别说了
All right, all right. Enough.
我说 "不行" 就是不行
I said, "No" and that's it.
你们知道吗 纳粹曾经给小孩进行眼球注射
Did you know that Nazis used to inject children's eyeballs
是为了看眼球会不会变色
to see if they would change color?
乔纳森
Jonathan!
谢谢
Thank you.
所以 你明天有何计划
So, what are your plans tomorrow?
梅根·梅勒妮要开万圣节派对
Megan Melanie's throwing a Halloween party.
不错啊
Thafs nice.
你和谁一起去 艾莉
Who are you going with, Allie?
布鲁克
And Brooke.
她要开车吗
She's not driving, is she?
我坐滴滴去
rm gonna take an Uber.
为啥 这样你就可以喝得大醉了吗
Why, so you can get shitfaced?
你觉得我笨吗 西恩娜
Who do you think I am, stupid, Sienna?
每次我出去玩我们都要像这样吵吗
Do we have to do this every time I go out?
我不喝酒的
You know I dont drink.
就要你说这句话
So you say.
你弟从不关好这些盒子
Your brother never closes these goddamn boxes.
给我 我来弄
Give me that. I got it.
妈 你有没有
Mom, do you ever…
好奇过乔纳森
wonder about Jonathan?
你想说什么
What do you mean?
你知道的
You know, he's…
他有点怪 所以呢
Hds an oddball. Soz what?
我之前进他房间时他在查找连环杀手
He was looking up serial killers when I went in his room before.
现在 他又谈论纳粹和大屠杀
Now, he's- he's talking about Nazis and the Holocaust.
- 我想说 - 这只是暂时的 西恩娜
-I mean- -It's just a phase, Sienna.
会过去的
It'll pass.
你一年前也是这么说的
You said that a year ago.
是啊 他失去了父亲
Yeah, well, he lost his father.
我不是吗
And I didn't?
你没看到我为了引起注意而哭泣
You don't see me crying out for attention.
我希望你能时不时地哭一会儿
Yeah, well, I wish you would from time to time.
你一直在压抑自己的情绪 这样不健康
You keep everything bottled up. it's not healthy.
行吧
All right.
你要是在他房间里发现动物尸体 可千万别惊讶
Just don't be surprised if you find a dead animal in his room.
说话当心点
You know what? Watch your mouth, huh?
那你呢
And what about you?
你爸带你去钓米诺鱼 还是石斑鱼时
When Daddy took you fishing for those midos or macos.
稣鱼
Minnows.
什么鱼不重要
Whatever they're called.
你爸发现你砍下鱼头
And he found you cutting the heads off.
你不会以为我忘了吧
Didn't think I'd remember that, did you?
那时的我比现在的乔纳森年龄小多了
I was a lot younger than Jonathan.
你那时已经够大了 能明辨是非了
Well, you were old enough to know the difference between right and wrong.
你弟没事的
Your brother's fine.
你有强力胶吗
Do you have any Super Glue?
有一点
A little.
- 怎么了 - 绳子断了
-Why, what happened? -The string came off.
我还以为你明天不会穿这个了
I thought you weren't gonna wear this tomorrow.
我不会涂脸
I wont paint my face then.
- 乔纳森 - 拜托
-Jonathan. -Come on.
现在来不及再买一套小丑服了
It's too late to get another costume.
给我
Give me.
天啊 你什么时候长这么高了
Jesus. What, did you grow another foot since dinner?
我是班上最高的
Tallest kid in my class.
好啊 但我还是可以揍你
Yeah, well, I can still kick your ass.
很快就没机会了
Not for long.
太恶心了
That is sick.
- 进度如何 - 刚把头骨弄好
-How much do you have left? -Just finishing up the skull.
看着真像爸爸画的
It looks just like Daddy's character.
你知道吗
You know?
你现在画得几乎和他一样好了
You draw almost as good as him now.
谢谢
Thanks.
这个也是你装扮的一部分吗
Is this a part of your costume, too?
不是 我才不会带那东西出门
No. I could not walk out in the streets with that thing.
我大概会在两秒钟内被逮捕
I'd get arrested in like two seconds.
对 但没人会惹你
Yeah. But nobody would mess with you.
- 那当然 - 好吧
-Thafs for sure. -Right.
小心 这把剑和剃须刀一样锋利
Just be careful, please. That blade's like razor sharp.
给 应该弄好了
There. Should be good now.
太好了
Awesome.
你觉得那家伙仍在逍遥法外吗
You think that guy's still out there?
谁
Who?
迈尔斯县的小丑
The Miles County clown.
这个小丑和你有什么关系吗
What's up with you and this clown all of a sudden?
你好似着了迷
YoiTre like obsessed.
他们一直没找到他的尸体
They never found his body.
要是他打算回来呢
What if he decides to come back here?
这就是你想打扮成他的原因吗
Is that why you wanna dress up like him?
你觉得如果他看到你穿着他的衣服
You think if he sees you wearing his costume,
就会对你很善良吗
he'll be all cordial with you?
善良？
Cordial?
友善
Friendly.
不会
No.
我才不会担心
I wouldn't worry about it.
要是他侥幸还活着
On the off chance that he is still alive,
我敢肯定他已经远离这里了
I'm sure he's gone far away from here.
- 非常感谢你帮我修帽子 - 不客气
-Thanks again for the hat. -You're welcome.
拍下面
Tap lower down.
欧文 我又看到它了
Owen, I saw it again.
你会帮他吗
Will you help this man?
你到那边去 喂饱他
You, over there! Yeah! Feed this man.
你呢 他饿了 你会喂他吗
How about you? He's hungry. Will you feed this man?
别无视他 喂他
He's not invisible. Feed him!
来自蜜李的新亚特脆片
New Art Crispies from Sugar Plum.
口口惊喜
Funz little surprises in every bite.
玻璃 虫子 还有刀片
Glass, insects, and razorblade.
谁也不知道你会吃到什么
There's no telling what you may find!
每盒都内含特殊奖品
Special prize included in every box.
哇 我想知道里面有什么
Wow! I wonder what I got!
孩子们 说到惊喜
Speaking of surprises, kids,
今天我们有一位特殊嘉宾
we have a very special guest with us today.
现在 他虽然不能说话
Now, for a guy who doesn't speak,
但却能引发巨大轰动
he sure makes a lot of noise.
他从迈尔斯县远道而来 请欢迎小丑 亚特
All the way from Miles County, please welcome Art the Clown.
都给我停下
Stop everything you're doing now!
我看到你们在狂吃 喂他 他太饿了
I see you feeding your faces. Feed him! He's so hungry.
喂饱他 喂饱他
Feed this man! Feed this man!
喂饱他
Feed this man!
操
Shit.
怎么回事
What's going on?
- 妈 - 快下楼
-Mom! -Get downstairs!
天啊
Jesus Christ!
妈 你在干嘛 快
Mom, what are you doing? Come on!
西恩娜 真的吗
Really, Sienna?
你把燃着的蜡烛放在梳妆台上一整晚
You left burning candles on your dresser all night?
你是傻子吗
What are you, fucking stupid?
我什么都没做 没点蜡烛
I didn't do anything. They weren't lit.
那请你给我解释一下
Then please explain to me
你那该死的房间是怎么着火的
how your goddamn room caught on fire.
- 我不知道 - 你不知道
-1 have no idea. - You have no idea.
这么说 是它自己燃烧起来的吗
So, it just spontaneously combusted out of thin air?
- 我觉得是的 -西恩娜
-I guess so. -Sienna
回去睡觉 你明早还要上学
Get back to bed. You have school in the morning.
- 我还得去上学吗 - 我刚才说了什么
-You mean I still have to go? -What did I say?
西恩娜 你知道吗
You know whatz Sienna?
总有一天我们会死在
You are going to kill us one of these days,
你的化学品和热风枪下
between your chemicals and your heat guns,
然后你熬夜到凌晨四点
and staying up until 4:00
谁都不知道你要干嘛
in the fucking morning doing God only knows what!
天哪 我说了一百遍了
Oh, my God. For the hundredth time,
我没有用化学品
I was not using chemicals
也没有把燃着的蜡烛放在梳妆台上
and I did not leave burning candles on my dresser!
- 你为什么就不相信我呢 - 因为…
-Why can't you just believe me? -Because...
今晚你睡我房间里 我睡沙发
Stay in my room tonight, and I'll sleep on the couch.
我不介意睡沙发
I don't mind sleeping on the couch.
去睡觉
Go to bed.
我把东西都放在最下面的抽屉里了
I kept whatever was in the bottom drawer.
大部分都被烧毁了
Most of ifs ruined.
你回家后一定要把车停在车库里
Make sure you park in the garage when you get home.
隔壁的那些动物 总是扔鸡蛋
Those animals next door are always throwing eggs
剃须膏
and shaving cream.
我不想让车被刮坏
I don't want the car getting scratched up.
你记得爸爸给我的那把剑吗
You know the sword Daddy got me?
怎么了
What about it?
昨晚那把剑出现在我梳妆台上
It was on top of my dresser last night.
或许可以修好那把剑
Well, maybe it can be restored.
烧坏了吗
Is it bad?
没有
It's fine.
完好无损
There's not a mark on it.
那就好
Thafs good.
你的衣服就没那么幸运了
Can't say the same for your clothes.
乔纳森 快点 你还有五分钟
Jonathan, hurry up. You have five minutes.
欢迎回到我们的节目
Welcome back to the program.
如果你在收看的话 我正与迈尔斯县大屠杀的
If you're just tuning in, I'm sitting here live
唯一幸存者坐在一起
with the sole survivor of the Miles County massacre,
屠杀已经过去整整一年
which occurred exactly one year ago today.
这个节目我做了很多年
I've worked on the show for many years,
但我从未与有和你相似经历的人
and Fve never sat across from someone
坐在一起
who has a story to tell quite like yours.
再次感谢你能抽出时间参加节目
Thank you again for taking the time to sit down
- 与我交谈 - 是我的荣幸
-and speak with me. -It's my pleasure.
我们之前说到
Now, when we left off, we were talking about the moment
你从昏迷中醒来
you woke up from the coma.
你还记得看到自己脸
Do you remember your initial reaction
的第一反应吗
when you first saw your face?
记得
Yes.
你想跟我们分享一下吗
Would you like to share that with us?
我宁愿自己当时就死掉
I wished I was dead.
你现在还这么想吗
Do you still feel that way?
人们会被我的长相吓 尤其是孩子们
People are frightened by the way that I look, especially children.
这对我来说很难熬
And it's really difficult for me to deal with that,
所以我最好别露面
so isolation is ideal.
那袭击者呢
Now, what about your attacker?
只证实了他叫小丑亚特
The man only identified as Art the Clown.
关于他的死亡
Well, there's a lot of controversy
争议很大
surrounding his supposed death.
当局发表声明
The authorities issued a statement,
称他的尸体在袭击发生后的第二天早上
claiming that his body disappeared
于县验尸官办公室消失
from the county coroner's office the morning after the attack.
他死了 我亲眼所见
He's dead. I saw it happen.
- 你们在干嘛呢 - 老兄 来看肖恩发现了什么
-What are you guys doing? -Dude, look what Sean found.
这是新的吉祥物
It's the new mascot.
天呐
Oh, man.
正合你意吧 乔纳森
Right up your alley, huh, J man?
我想知道它是怎么死的
I wonder how it died.
可能是吃了学校的烘肉卷
Probably had the school meatloaf.
我看你还是别动它了
I think you should leave it alone.
怎么了 他又不介意
What for? He doesn't mind.
太恶心了
Its so'gross.
老兄 可惜你没看到
Dude, you should have been here.
之前有几只鸟在啄食它屁股呢
Couple of birds were eating his asshole.
没错
Yeah.
看好了 斯蒂芬妮
Watch this. Stephanie!
斯蒂芬妮 过来一下
Stephanie! Come here for a minute.
肖恩 别这样
Sean, come on.
有好戏看了
It's gonna be awesome.
- 怎么了 - 看看
-What's up? - Check it out.
有只猫在垃圾箱后面生了几只崽
Some cat just gave birth behind the dumpster.
- 真的吗 - 是的
-Really? - Yeah.
去看看那些小猫咪
Go look at all the kittens.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God!
怎么了 蛆虫也需要关爱的
What's wrong? Maggots need love, too!
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie!
你能
Can you?
怎么了
Whafs going on?
该死 是普林西比女士
Oh, shit. Ms. Principe.
你们在后面干嘛呢
What are you boys doing back here?
天呐 亨德森先生
Oh, Christ. Mr. Henderson.
- 没什么 - 真的吗
-Nothing. - Really?
你马上去把柯蒂斯先生找来
You go find Mr. Curtis right now,
让他把这些处理掉
and you have him move that.
还有你俩去上课
And you two, get to class.
处理掉
Move it!
乔纳森
Jonathan.
专心看自己的卷子
Keep your eyes on your own paper.
惠伦先生
Mr. Whalen.
我可以出去一下吗
May I be excused?
等下 我好像忘拿短裤了
Wait. I think I forgot my shorts.
我应该有多着的
I think I have an extra pair.
- 你有多着的衬衫吗 - 应该有
-Do you have an extra shirt? -I might.
我们可以去厕所
We can go to the bathroom...
喂 不要在走廊里乱跑
Hey! No running in the hallways!
乔纳森 给我回来
Jonathan, get back here!
天呐
Oh, my God.
万圣节快乐 宝贝
Happy Halloween, my pretty.
- 这会儿吃巧克力太早了吧 - 嗯
-Little early for chocolate, no? -Mm.
我可是经常吃
You're talking to someone who eats Count Chocula
巧古拉伯爵麦片的
on a regular basis.
我们能不讨论麦片了吗
Can we not talk about cereal?
拜托
Please?
好吧
Okay.
今早 有人心情不好哟
Someone's in a mood this morning.
抱歉
Sorry.
昨晚基本没睡
Barely slept last night.
我来猜猜
Let me guess.
你熬到凌晨四点
You were up until 4:00 in the morning,
又在弄万圣节服装
working on that Halloween costume again.
其实 是将近六点
Actually, it was more like 6:00.
你们今早听说莫尼卡·布朗的事了吗
Did you guys hear about Monica Brown this morning?
啊 那个讨人厌的脱口秀主持人吗
Ugh! That bitchy talk show host?
对 那个讨人厌的脱口秀主持人脸被撕烂了
Yeah, that bitchy talk show host totally got her face torn off.
什么
What?
好吧 听着
Okay, get this.
她之前采访了那个迈尔斯县的幸存者
So, she had that Miles County survivor on.
你还记得那个昏迷的人吗
Do you remember the one who was in the coma
她的脸也血肉模糊 她叫什么来着
and her face was all mutilated? Whafs her name?
好像是 我不确定 维多利亚 还是什么
It was like, I don't know, Victoria or something.
- 维多利亚·海斯 - 对
-Victoria Heyes? - Yes.
她在节目上崩溃了
She had a meltdown on the show, right?
然后在后台发疯了
And then backstage, she went full-on psycho,
赤手空拳殴打莫尼卡·布朗
and mauled Monica Brown with her bare hands.
- 不是吧 - 天呐
-No way. -Oh, my God.
她死了吗
Is she dead?
我觉得 死了算她运气好
I mean, if she's lucky.
什么 你见过那些面部移植
What? You ever see photos of those transplant faces,
看起来像土豆先生的照片吗
looking like Mr. Potato Head?
- 去他妈的 - 天呐 真有那么糟糕吗
-Fuck that shit. -God, is it really that bad?
我还没看到照片
Well, I haven't seen photos.
但我听说
But from what I hear,
她有点像我吃的饼干
she kinda looks like the inside of my cookie.
她的眼睛都被挖出来了
Her eyes are all gouged out.
她的鼻子就像从脸上掉下来似的
And her nose was like falling off of her face.
老天
Oh, my God.
我听说她有一小块脸
And I heard that her cheek
在维多利亚·海斯的鞋底
like a little bit, was found at the bottom of Victoria Heyes1 shoe.
你还好吗
You okay?
西恩娜
Sienna?
嘿 你没事吗
Hey, you all right?
我没想用莫尼卡·布朗的破事
I really didn't mean to freak you out
吓唬你的
with that Monica Brown shit.
- 抱歉 - 没事
-I'm so sorry. -No.
- 你没事吧 - 没事我很好没事
-You okay? - I'm okay, I'm okay. Tm fine.
我只是需要缓一下
I just--1 just need a second I think.
嗨 打扰一下
Hi. Excuse me.
请问你能别管闲事吗
Can you mind your own business, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我的天 西恩娜 跟我说说话
My God. Sienna, talk to me.
怎么回事
What's going on?
昨晚我家失火了
We had- we had a fire last night.
- 什么哪里起火 - 我房间
-What? Where? - My room.
我一定是点着蜡烛睡着了
I must've fallen asleep with the candles burning.
- 真的很糟 - 好吧 "很遭"是有多遭
-It was pretty bad. -Okay. How bad is "pretty bad"?
火烧屋顶的程度
Like flames touching the ceiling,
整个房子都有可能烧成灰烬
entire house could have burned down bad.
- 老天 大家都没事吗 - 嗯 还好没事
-Jesus. Is everyone okay? -Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
我妈妈及时把火扑灭了
No, my mom put the flames out in time.
哇哦 该死的芭芭拉过来救了我们
Wow. Fucking Barbara to the rescue.
她简直就是个女超人
I swear that woman's a superhero.
- 她生气了吗 - 大发雷霆
-Was she pissed? -Livid.
今早训了我整整一个半小时
Berated me for a good hour and a half this morning.
其实 也没那么糟啦
I mean, thafs not so bad.
你差点在他们睡觉的时候
I mean, you did almost torch the whole family
烧了全家
in their sleep.
听着 重要的是没人受伤 对吧
Look. The important thing is that nobody got hurt. Right?
说真的 几周后 你想起这件事
Seriously, in a few weeks, you'll be laughing
- 都会觉得搞笑 - 也可能是几个月后
-about the whole thing. -More like months.
- 行吧 几个月 - 也可能是一年后
-Okay. A couple months. -Probably a year.
其实不只是失火
It wasrTt just the fire.
就
It...
昨晚还发生了很怪的事
Something really strange happened last night.
什么事
What?
没什么 没事
Nothing. Nothing. I'm fine.
- 你确定 - 嗯 没事
-You sure? -Yeah. Yeah.
对 没事 行了呃
Yeah, no, come on. Um…
我们回去吧
Let's- let's go back.
我的饭可能冷透了
Now, that my food is probably ice cold.
你想吃一块我的莫卮韦·布朗饼干吗
You want a piece of my Monica Brown cookie?
- 布鲁克 - 抱歉
-Brooke. -Sorry.
你很烦
I hate ydu.
谢谢 警官
Thank you, Officer.
抱歉给您添麻烦了
I'm so sorry to cause you trouble.
没事的 祝您愉快 女士
No problem. Have a nice day, ma'am.
你也是
You, too.
- 回你房间 - 但是妈妈 我
-Get to your room. -But mom, I--
去你房间
Go to your room.
我开口前我一个字
I don't wanna hear another word out of you
都不想听你说
until I say so.
真不敢相信我沦落到
I can't believe I'm reduced
只能买一对廉价翅膀了
to a pair of cheap store-bought wings.
你觉得翅膀小吗
You think these are too small?
你想要多大呢
How big do you want 'em?
翅膀大的话 你很可能会碰翻
You're gonna be knocking over people's drinks
别人的饮料
and shit all night.
我觉得你的翅膀很可爱
I think they're cute.
好吧 也没那么糟啦
Well, they're not terrible.
你确实也没别的可选了
You don't really have a choice.
是我妈妈打来的
Ugh, ts my mom.
你跟你妈妈说我们今晚要去哪
Where did you tell your mother we were going tonight?
梅根·梅兰妮的万圣节派对
Megan Melanie's Halloween party.
好 我在门口等你
Okay. Ill catch you out front.
好的
Okay.
嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
好的
Good.
没有 我只是跟西恩娜在城里
No, I'm just in town with Sienna.
你什么时候回来 因为
What time are you gonna be home? Because-
抱歉
Sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好的
Nice.
没什么 我刚刚碰到一个穿着
Nothing. I just ran into a man
恐怖小丑服的人
wearing terrifying clown costume.
需要我帮你找什么吗
Can I help you find anything?
需要帮忙吗
Need any help?
你没事吧
Uh, find everything okay?
没事
Yeah. Mmhmm.
我得扫码
I'm gonna need to scan those.
哦 呃 好的 抱歉
Oh. Um, right. Sorry.
没事
It's all good.
好的 一共32.25美元
Okay. That'll be 32.25.
好的 呃
Yeah, um…
我好像把包落在楼下了
I think I left my bag downstairs.
你非要把那玩意儿放嘴里的话
If you're gonna put that in your mouth,
得付钱
you gotta pay for it.
给
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
等下 我给你拿个大袋子
You know what? Pm gonna go get you a big bag.
哦 不用 我得
Oh, no, no. I- I really-
- 我不需要 - 没事 没关系的
-1 don't--1 don't need it. - No, no, ifs fine.
袋子就放在后面
I got 'em right back here.
行吧
Okay.
拜托 不要
Please don't.
停下 快停下 求你
Stop. Please stop! Please!
嘿 老兄
Hey, buddy?
能别在这里捣乱了吗
You wanna quit causin1 trouble?
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
-Thank you. -Thank you.
-万圣节快乐-你也是
-Happy Halloween. - You, too.
哥们儿 我们打灯了
Yo, we closin1 up, man.
你要买什么
Can I help you find something?
8.99美元
8.99.
你认真的吗
Are you serious right now?
你到底付不付钱
Yo, can you pay for that or not?
先生 你在干嘛
Sir, what are you doing?
行了 先生 我要报警了
All right. Sir, you know what? I'm gonna call the police.
嘿 没听见我说话吗
Hey! Did you hear what I said?
给我滚出去 不然别怪我不客气
Get the hell outta here before I fuck you up.
这也太他妈离谱了
Thafs fucking crazy.
我跟你说了就是他 艾莉
I'm telling you it was him, Allie.
甚至连鼻尖上的小黑点
Right down to the little black dot
都完美契合
on the tip of his nose.
西恩娜 你自己说的
Sienna, you said it yourself.
今晚会有好多傻逼
I mean, there are gonna be hundreds
穿成那个疯子的样子
of douchebags dressed up as that psycho tonight.
就连你弟弟也在说要扮演他
Even your brother was talking about going as him.
我不是说你弟弟是傻逼啊
Not that I'm calling your brother a douchebag.
就是个巧合而已
It's just a coincidence.
那你要怎么解释那场火
Then how do you explain the fire?
我之前梦到了
I dreamt it and it happened.
你最近换药了吗
Did you change medications recently?
天啊 我没发疯
Jesus Christ. Tm not crazy!
深呼吸
Take a breath.
我就是说 你有没有考虑过
I- Tm just saying, did you ever consider
更合理的解释是那场大火导致了噩梦
the logical explanation that maybe the fire
而不是噩梦导致了大火
caused your nightmare, not the other way around?
什么
What?
我认为在你睡着的时候房间起火了
I think that the fire started while you were sleeping.
火一路烧进你的梦里
And it worked its way into your nightmare.
意思是说 你的身体肯定感受到火焰了
I mean, your body must've felt the flames.
发生这种破事很正常
You know shit like that happens all the time.
嘿 你要买糖或什么吗
Look, are you getting candy or what?
我都不知道我们在这干嘛
I mean, what are- what are we doing here?
就算你说的是真的
Even if that is the case,
火灾的起因也没得到解释
it doesn't explain how the fire started.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, honey.
哦 我天 他们关店了
Oh, my. They're closed.
- 哇 哦 - 哦
-Wow. -Oh.
你看呀 妈妈
Look at that, Mom.
看到了 真不错啊 宝贝
Yeah, thafs wonderful, honey.
好酷
Cool.
行了 我们走吧 走吧
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
不然你能看上一整天呢
You're just gonna stay here the whole time.
走吧
Come on.
我们不直接和保险公司打交道
We don't go direct with our insurers.
好吧 先给我你的邮政编码
Okay, but let me get your zip code.
我帮你在当地找个中间人
I'm gonna find a broker in your area.
你怎么在家啊
What are you doing home?
他在这里 西恩娜
He's here, Sienna.
谁
Who?
迈尔斯县的小丑
The Miles County clown.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我今天在学校里看见他了
I saw him today in my school.
和警察公布的照片一模一样
Just like in the police photos.
慢慢说
Slow down.
真的是他
It was him.
今晚会有很糟糕的事情发生
Something really bad is gonna happen tonight.
这是爸爸的速写本吗
Is that Daddy's sketchbook?
看这个
Look here.
你啥时候拿到它的
How long have you had this?
乔纳森 回答我
Jonathan, answer me.
你知道的 我们一直在找这本子
You know how long weVe been looking for this.
看这里
Read this.
我今天看到她了 就是这个女孩
I saw her today. This exact girl.
但她看起来不像人类
Only she didn't look human.
她和老嘉年华还有迈尔斯县的 小丑之间
There's some kinda connection between her, the old carnival,
一定有某种联系
and the Miles County clown.
我能预料到 今晚真的会有很糟糕的事情发生
Something really bad's gonna happen tonight. I know it.
这些是你画的吗
Did you put these in here?
不是
No.
但你看这里
But look at this.
这就是他
It's him!
爸爸画的吗
Daddy drew this?
这还不是全部
Thafs not all.
万一 你也是其中的一部分呢
What if you're connected, too?
什么
What?
乔纳森 你疯了
Jonathan, you're acting crazy.
你痫了 好吧
You're acting crazy. Okay?
他专门为你设计了这个形象
He created this character for you.
还在临死前把那柄剑给了你
He gave you that sword right before he died.
就好像他知道会发生什么一样
It's like he saw this coming.
爸爸给我画过很多东西
Daddy drew a lot of things for me.
也给我买过一堆没用的东西
He bought me tons of shit.
说真的 你是怎么了啊
Seriously, whafs wrong with you?
- 你听听你在说什么 - 发生什么事了
-Do you even hear yourself? -What's going on in here?
他给你看过这个了吗
Did he show you this?
她才不管呢
She doesn't care.
她还在气头上呢 因为我可能要被休学了
She's just pissed, 'cause I might get suspended.
休学 为啥
Suspended. For what?
你还没和她说呢
Oh, you didn't tell her?
今早你弟弟把一只死动物带进了学校
Your brother brought a dead animal to school this morning.
- 什么 - 没错
-What? - Yeah.
一只死动物 你敢信吗
A dead animal. Can you believe it?
他把大厅搞得一团糟
He vandalized the halls.
他们和我说的时候
I almost had a fucking heart attack
我他妈的心脏病都要犯了
when they told me.
不是我 是小丑干的
It wasn't me. It was the clown.
是那个小女孩把死动物带进来的
The little girl brought it in.
关于这个天杀的小丑 我一个字都不想再听到
I don't wanna hear another word about this goddamn clown.
他回来的时候手上和衣服上
He was covered in blood on his shirt and his hands
全是血
when he got here.
满手是血被校长抓了个正着
The principal literally caught you red-handed.
那是因为他把动物朝我身上丢
Thafs 'cause he threw it at me.
我就该听你的
I should've listened to you.
关于这个孩子的事
You have been telling me over and over again
你已经和我说过很多遍了
about this kid.
我周一就给希夫林医生打电话
Pm calling Dr. Schiffrin on Monday.
不能再这样下去了
I'm putting a stop to this now.
还有给我把你的碗放水槽里去
And put your goddamn bowl in the sink.
我不会再说第二遍了
I'm not telling you again.
真的是他
It was him.
你得相信我
You gotta believe me.
乔纳森
Jonathan.
这可能
It was-
这可能就是些学校里的孩子 在捣乱吧
it was probably just some kids at school, messing around.
正好一周年了
It's the one-year anniversary.
而且一小时前
I mean, I already saw some...
我就在咒语商店看到一个穿着同款衣服的傻蛋
jerk wearing that same costume in Abracadabra an hour ago.
那这些画和文章又要怎么解释
What about these drawings and these articles then?
我们都知道爸爸当时是怎么回事
We both know what happened to Daddy.
他没有错
Okay, none of this was his fault.
这些不好的东西
And all of these ugly things in here,
也代表不了他
thafs not who he was.
他爱你
He loved you...
很爱你
very much.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be okay.
- 今晚呆在家吧 - 乔纳森
-Stay home tonight. -Jonathan.
求你 算我求你了
Please. Tm begging you.
- 不会有事的 - 行吧
-Nothing's gonna happen. - Fine.
那今晚一堆人被杀的时候
Just don't act surprised when a bunch of people
可别太惊讶
get killed tonight.
你有没有…
Have you ever...
我相信他
I believe him.
信他什么
About what?
我信他没有把学校搞得一团糟
I don't think he vandalized the school.
哦 现在 你又信他了
Oh, now, you believe him?
昨天他还是黄道十二宫杀手呢［60年代的美国连环杀手］
Yesterday, he was the Zodiac Killer.
你怎么改变想法了
Whafs changed?
去开门
Get the door.
由于近期爆发的大肠杆菌传播
Restaurants on the East Coast
东海岸的一些餐厅
have recalled romaine lettuce
召回了一批长叶生菜
due to a recent E. Coli outbreak.
至少十二人被送医治疗
At least 12 people have been hospitalized
其中两人情况危急
and two are in critical condition.
- 嗨 - 不给糖就捣蛋
-Hi. -Trick or treat!
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween.
我喜欢你的妆容
Oh, I love your makeup.
全是她自己画的
Oh, she did it all herself.
哇哦 真棒
Wow! Great job.
你要说什么呀
What do you say?
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
- 拜拜 - 拜拜
-Bye. -Bye.
啊 你这个年纪还来要糖是不是不太合适啊
Ah, aren't you a little old to be trick or treating?
等等
Wait a minute.
你不就是服装店里的那个人吗
Aren't you that guy from the costume shop?
还真是
You are?
你在这干嘛 哦
What are you doing here? Oh.
你是住在这附近吗 还是
Seriously, do you live around here or something?
你很奇怪 你知道吗
You're really weird, you know that?
我懂的 老兄
Yeah. Look, I get itz dude.
你这一整套诡异的默剧表演
The whole creepy, silent mime gimmick.
还挺有节目效果
I mean, it's very effective.
血迹更是画龙点睛
And the blood is a nice touch also.
不过 我什么都给不了你
Yeah. I can't give you anything.
不行 抱歉 真的 成年人没资格拿糖
No, I'm sorry. Really. No- no candy for grownups.
别闹了
Come on.
走开
Go away.
烦人精 去烦别人吧
Seriously, asshole, go bother somebody else.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me right now?
我说了 快滚 我认真的
I said, get out of here. I mean it.
等等 那 如果我给你糖的话 你就会走吗
Wait. So, if I give you candy, you'll leave?
行吧
Fine.
拿着 万圣节快乐
Here. Happy Halloween.
来看另一条新闻
In other news,
脱口秀主持人 莫妮卡·布朗
talk show provocateur, Monica Brown
时至今夜仍未脱离险境
is still in critical condition this evening,
今天早些时候她在KLA演播室
following a violent attack which took place
遭到了猛烈的袭击
at KLA Studios earlier today.
这位节目主持人在直播结束后
The TV host was violently assaulted
被她的嘉宾维多利亚·海斯在化妆间里
in her dressing room after a live broadcast
剧烈殴打
with guest Victoria Heyes.
海斯是2017年迈尔斯县大屠杀里唯一的幸存者
Heyes is the sole survivor of the Mills County massacre
当时有八人遇难
of 2017, which left eight people dead
而海斯则身受重伤
and Heyes in critical condition.
这位二十岁的犯罪嫌疑人被当场逮捕
The 20-year-old was arrested at the crime scene,
并由当局带走拘留
and taken into custody by authorities.
由于布朗有利用受害人的嫌疑
The interview sparked controversy
此前的采访也饱受争议
upon its announcement given Brown's exploitative tendencies.
昨晚 海斯从圣迈克尔医院出院了
Heyes was released from St. Michael's Hospital
她在医院里进行了几个月的治疗
yesterday evening after months of rehabilitation
与心理分析
and psychoanalysis.
和你一样 西恩娜
Like you, Sienna.
万圣节终于到来了
Halloween is officially here.
成千上万的人们纷纷来到
and thousands are lining up for the parade
纽约东村参加游行
in New York City's East Village.
这里天气预计将会寒冷多雨
Weather conditions are expected to be cold and rainy,
如果您想要参加 请务必多穿衣物
so dress warm if you're planning to attend.
不 不
No! No!
不
No!
不 不
No, no!
强尼
Johnny!
你还在害怕
You're still afraid.
别说了 我认真的
Stop it now. I mean it.
他们要来找你了 芭芭拉
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
怎样
Well?
别说了 你什么都不知道
Stop it! You're ignorant.
他们要来找你了 芭芭拉
They're coming for you, Barbara.
太暴露了
It's revealing.
别说了
Stop it.
我花了三个月做的
Three months worth of work,
你就只说一句太暴露了
and all you can say is it's revealing?
你的胸都要走光了
Your tits are practically popping out.
没有
They are not!
就有转过去
They are! Turn around.
他来了
Here he comes now.
强尼
Johnny!
你知道 我做的是谁的服装吗
You know what I was making?
是爸爸创作的角色
It's Daddy's character.
是 但在书上看到
Yes, but seeing it on paper
和在女儿身上看到就是两码事了
and seeing it on your daughter are two different things.
你看起来就像要去当脱衣舞娘
You look like you're going to a strip club.
妈 现在万圣节大家都这么穿
Mom, this is how people dress on Halloween these days.
你知道我为了这件衣服
Do you have any idea how much work
付出了多少心血吗
I put into this?
你确实做得很不错
You did an excellent job.
但从什么时候开始 万圣节也要穿得这么性感了
But when did Halloween become synonymous with sex?
你太保守了
You'rs such a prude.
好了 我叫的车到了 再见
Okay. That's my ride. Later.
西恩娜
Sienna.
你爸会喜欢的
Dad would have loved it.
我走了
Bye.
艾莉
Allie!
你有发糖果吗
Have you been handing out candy?
我看碗里还是满的
That bowl is still filled to the brim.
艾莉
Allie!
天呐
Oh, my God.
艾莉
Allie?
艾莉 艾莉 你说话呀
Allie? Allie, answer me.
你在哪
Where are you?
艾莉
Allie?
哦 不
Oh, no! No, no! No! No!
妈妈
Mom.
我说什么来着
What'd I tell you?
我可没怀疑过你
I never doubted you for a second.
快点 我们去鬼混吧
Come on. Let's go get fucked up.
两位喝点什么
What can I get you guys?
伏特加和可乐 谢谢
Uh, vodka and coke, please.
你要喝什么
What do you want?
别看手机了 你要喝什么
Off your phone. What do you want?
朗姆酒混可乐
Uh, rum and coke. Mixed.
然后再给我们来两杯威士忌 好吗 谢谢
Also, can we have two shots of whiskey, please? Thank you.
艾莉给你回消息了吗
Has Allie texted you back yet?
没有
No.
你再看下嘛
Well, can you check?
依然没有
Negative.
这不是她的风格
You know this isn't like her.
没事的
It's fine.
放轻松
Just relax.
就单纯享受一下你人生的大好时光 行不
And have a good time for once in your life, okay?
我还是给她妈妈发个短信吧 她会回我的
Maybe if I just text her mom, she will get back to me.
不 别看手机了
No. Off your phone.
- 关掉 - 好吧
-Phone down, -Okay!
- 我们玩我们的 - 嗯
-Look, we're gonna have fun. -Mmhmm.
- 别那么紧张 - 好
-Stress-free environment. -Yep.
- 拿酒 - 好
-Take this. -Okay.
- 走吧 - 好 谢谢
-Lets go. -All right. Thank you.
让我过一下 抱歉
Will you excuse me? Sorry.
- 走吧 - 好
-Let's go. -Okay. Yep.
好了
Okay.
敬闺蜜之夜
To a great night with my girls.
- 敬闺蜜之夜 - 万圣节快乐
-To a great night. -Happy Halloween.
土
Oh, God.
你是真不会喝酒啊
Oh, you're such an amateur.
真不知道你怎么喝得下去这玩意儿的
I do not know how you drink that shit.
喝多了就习惯了
Well, chase it.
混蛋
Oh, you asshole!
万圣节快乐 亲爱的
Happy Halloween, baby.
你好辣哦
You look hot.
真的吗 你喜欢我的发型吗
Oh, yeah? You like my hair?
喜欢 你做了多久
I do. How long did that take?
你不会想知道的
You don't wanna know.
衣服不错
Yeah, nice shirt.
痴心妄想
Wishful thinking.
我就知道
I bet!
杰夫
Ohz Jeff.
这是我最好的朋友西恩娜
This is my best friend Sienna.
你好
Hi.
哇 你这身很牛逼啊
Wow. That is a badass outfit.
谢谢
Thank you.
这姑娘真的天赋异禀
This girl is unbelievably talented.
你绝对想不到
You have no idea.
这一身从头到脚都是她亲手做的
She made this whole thing herself, head to toe.
你做了多久来着 五个月吗
What did it take you, like five months?
没有 没那么久
No. It didn't take that long.
就是 有
Yes, it did.
你不知道 你好像做了一辈子
You have no idea. It took forever.
你太了不起了
You are unbelievable.
说实话 我感觉你完全抢了我的风头
You know, honestly, I feel upstaged.
好吧
Okay.
你俩能消停会儿吗
Could you guys please stop?
都要把我夸害羞了
You're making me feel a little self-conscious, so...
多喝几杯就不害羞了
Oh. Well, a couple of shots will help that.
- 喝 喝 喝 喝 - 喝 喝 喝 喝
-Oh! Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots! -Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
不 我今晚不能再喝了
No. No, no, no. I cannot drink anymore tonight.
我妈肯定会气死的 那我就完了
My mom will get so pissed if I get fucked up.
她不会的
No, she won't!
你妈肯定过两个小时就睡了
Your momK gonna be asleep in two hours.
不行
I can't do it.
好吧
Okay, fine.
帮我们俩拍张照
Take a picture of us.
好
Okay.
来跳舞吧
Ooh, let's dance!
好
Okay.
- 不给糖就捣蛋 - 不给糖就捣蛋
-Trick or treat! -Trick or treat!
孩子们 好酷啊
Kids, look how cool!
天呐
Oh my God!
太酷了
So cool.
我这个怎么黏黏的
Why is mine so sticky?
别担心 假血而已啦
Don't worry. It's just fake blood.
放包里吧
Just put it in the bag.
我喜欢
Ooh, I like it.
好啦 谢谢
All right, thank you!
谢谢
Thank you!
走吧 万圣节快乐
Lefs go. Happy Halloween!
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween!
你在干什么
What are you doing in here?
你想看电影吗
You wanna watch a movie?
楼下还有很多剩的糖果
There is a lot of candy leftover downstairs.
来嘛 我允许你熬夜
Come on. TH let you stay up late.
别来烦我
Go away.
乔纳森
Jonathan.
我很抱歉 你今晚的计划被毁了
I am sorry that your plans were ruined tonight.
真的
I really am.
但你今天在学校闯祸的时候
But you should've thought about this
怎么没想到会变成这样呢
before you pulled that shit in school today.
再胡闹 就不讨喜了
I mean, enough's enough.
我跟你说实话了
I told you the truth.
- 别让我再重复一遍 - 不是我干的
-I'm not doing this again. - It wasn't me!
倘若不是你 我就向你真诚道歉
Well, if it wasn't you, then I sincerely apologize.
但我不会再相信你了
But I just don't believe you anymore.
那这个呢
What about this?
又是这本破书
Again with this fucking book!
为什么爸爸要收集这些新闻
Why was Daddy collecting these news articles?
"嘉年华上发现被害女孩”还有这个
"Slain girl found at carnival." And this?
看看这些涂鸦
Look at these drawings!
这根本不像爸爸
This isn't like Daddy!
他生病了
He was sick.
你怎么就不懂呢
Why can't you understand?
他不知道他自己是谁
He didn't know who he was,
有一半的时间他都不知道自己在做什么
or what he was doing half the time.
这个
And this.
这他妈只是一个记事本而已
This bullshit is nothing but a fucking reminder.
不
No!
我再也不要看到它出现在我家里
I want this out of my house.
你有病吧
You're such a bitch!
你再说一次试试
Don't you ever say that to me again!
乔纳森 乔纳森 你给我回来
Jonathan. Jonathan, you get back here.
乔纳森
Jonathan!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你要去干什么
Wait. Where are you going?
我再拿杯酒
I'm gonna grab a drink.
- 我能和你来张自拍吗 - 当然
-Yof can I get a selfie? -Sure.
牛逼 姑娘
Fuck, yeah, girl!
什么
What?
天呐
Oh, my God.
西恩娜
Sienna!
- 嗨 - 嗨
-Hey!-Hi!
终于找到你了
I missed you, girl.
嗨
Hi.
等等
No, wait.
感受一下
Feel this.
- 真是... - 太神奇了
-How…-...amazing is that!
- 绝了 - 不 等一下
-Oh, my God. -No, no. Wait.
你没明白 我想要这个
You don't understand. I want it.
- 我知道 - 我想要
-I know. -I wanna like...
住在里面 你懂吗
live in it, you know?
- 你感觉怎样 - 不错
-How are you feeling? -Good.
是吗
Yeah?
- 相当不错 - 好
-So good actually! -Okay.
我感觉
I feel like...
酒的后劲上来了
that shot's really starting to hit me.
威士忌就是这样
Well, whiskey will do that to you.
- 我需要这种感觉 - 是啊
-I needed this. -Yeah.
你是对的
You were right.
- 你真的是对的 - 是的
-You were so right. -Yeah.
我就是需要出来透口气 停止思考
I needed to just, like get out, and stop thinking,
不再为生活里的琐碎焦虑
worrying about every little thing in my life.
比如这件服装
Like- like this costume.
是啊
Yeah.
- 对 - 你知道吗
-Yeah. - You know?
让我想起了我爸
It reminds me of my Dad.
他以前经常
He used to-
我小时候他经常给我画这个角色
he used to draw this character for me when I was a little girl.
他常对我说
He used to tell me I was gonna grow up
我长大后会像她一样
to be like her one day.
我对此深信不疑
And I really believed it.
看看 现在的你
Well, look at you now!
你就是她
You are her.
我一点都不像她
I am nothing like her.
我既胆小
I'm not courageous.
又懦弱
I'm not brave.
我是说 我现在感觉就像是
I mean, I literally had a panic attack today
在学校时当着所有人的面惊慌失措一样
in school in front of everybody.
我在你的酒里加了点摇头丸
I put molly in your drink.
什么
What?
对 我放了半片在你的酒里
I did. I put a half a tablet in your drink,
另外半片放进了我的酒里
the other half in mine.
这算不上毒品 根本不沾边儿
Not even really, it was kind of nothing.
但效果很好 因为我还在药劲儿上
But it's fine, 'cause Pm also on it.
所以我们都没事
So, we're totally fine. You and me.
这就是为什么你觉得自己好像嗑药了一样
And that is why you feel like you're on molly.
因为你确实嗑药了
'Cause you are.
就现在
Right now.
你这该死的贱人
You fuckin' bitch!
什么鬼
What the...
真是一团糟
That is so messed up!
我这么做是为了让你感觉好些
I did it. I made you feel better, didn't I?
我他妈快气疯了
I'm fucking pissed.
不 别生气
No, don't be pissed.
你一直在笑 你怎么会气疯呢
You're smiling. You can't be pissed.
不 贱人 我没有笑
No, bitch. Tm not smiling.
你这明显就是在笑
You're totally smiling.
来 我们得出去了 我们去跳舞
So, we gotta go back out, and we gotta dance.
乔纳森
Jonathan.
乔纳森 求你回来
Jonathan, please get back.
乔纳森
Jonathan!
该死
Oh shit.
怎么了
What?
我妈给我打了五六个电话
My mom called me like six times.
- 噢 别回她 - 我得看看
-Ooh. Do not call her back. -I'm gonna see-
- 别回她电话 - 嘘 安静
-Don't call her back! -Shh, shh, shh!
西恩娜 西恩娜
Sienna. Sienna.
- 西恩娜 - 嘿
-Sienna. -Hey!
- 挂掉 - 他死定了 西恩娜
-Stop it. - Hers dead, Sienna!
等会什么
Wait. What?
挂断电话
Cut the call.
等等 妈妈 我听不见你说话
Wait, mom. Mom, I can't hear you.
稍等
Just-
呃 抱歉
Um, sorry.
你刚刚说什么
Um, whafd you say?
他把我的车涂满了剃须膏
He covered the entire fucking car with shaving cream!
什么
What?
对 这事儿就他妈离谱
Yeah! The whole fucking thing.
剃须膏 还有厕纸和鸡蛋 他死定了
Shaving cream, toilet paper, eggs. He's dead!
他
H e--
乔纳森不会那样做的
Jonathan wouldn't do that.
对 他不会这样做
Yeah. He didn't do this.
就像今早他也没有故意破坏学校一样
Just like he didn't vandalize the school this morning!
看 这儿乱的 不
Look at this. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
这太离谱了
This- this is crazy now.
他必须立刻去看心理医生
He's going to that psychiatrist immediately.
我再也受不了他了
I cannot deal with him anymore.
不至于吧 妈妈
Really, mom?
就因为他涂了点剃须膏在你车上
You're gonna send him to a shrink
你就要把他送去
because what, he put like a little bit of shaving cream
看心理医生
on your car?
我还真欣慰你居然觉得这事儿很有趣 西恩娜
I'm glad you think this is funny, Sienna.
就是些剃须膏而已
It's just shaving cream.
他又不是用棒球棒
It's not like he took a baseball bat
砸了你的挡风玻璃
to your windshield.
现在可是万圣节
It's Halloween. I mean…
你喝多了吗
Are you drunk?
- 没有 - 我看你就是喝多了
-No. - Yes, you are.
我听得出来你声音不对劲 你喝了多少
I can hear it in your voice. How many drinks have you had?
我们不是在说乔纳森的事嘛
I--1 thought we were talking about Jonathan.
西恩娜 那你帮帮我
Sienna, so help me,
赶紧回来帮我 把家里的其他东西都擦一遍
if you come home plastered on top of everything else
- 我今晚一直在忙活这事儿 - 不
-I'm dealing with tonight- - No.
我发誓我没喝多 我甚至可以去吹测酒仪
I swear to God, I'm not drunk. TH even take a breathalyzer.
你这是要逼死我
You're killing me.
你知道不
You know that?
你和你弟弟都是一个德行 我受够了
You and your brother both, I have had it.
我爱你
I love you.
嗯 西恩娜 我这是在警告你
Yeah, Sienna, I am warning you.
不 我说真的 妈妈
No. Really, mom.
我爱你 我…
I- I love you. I...
我也爱你
I love you, too.
去享受你的派对吧 我很抱歉打扰你
Go and enjoy your party. I'm- I'm sorry to bother you.
听着
And listen.
不论发生什么乔纳森都会没事的
Everything will be okay with Jonathan.
我保证
I promise.
记着我说过的话就行
Just remember what I said.
回家路上小心 好吗
Be careful getting home, all right?
我会的 再见
I will. Bye.
万圣节快乐 混球们
Happy Halloween, motherfuckers!
- 你妈怎么说 - 没事了
-How'd it go? -Fine.
好吧
All right.
现在我来教你点嗑药的规矩
Let me give you a little molly etiquette here.
规矩一 你永远不要
Rule number one, you never
在嗑药的时候打电话给你妈
ever call your mother when you're rolling on molly.
听清了吗 千万别打给你妈 好吗
Okay? Your mother, never. All right?
规矩二
Rule number two,
千万别他妈浪费药效 来吧
you don't fucking let it go to waste. Come on.
看这儿乱的
Look at this.
他真的以为自己能若无其事
Did he really think he was gonna get away with this?
他很快就会幡然醒悟
He is in for a rude awakening.
事情变得不一样了
Things are gonna change.
你看见了吗
Do you see that?
看 在那 那个小女孩
There. There. That little girl.
她在说什么
What is she saying?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我发誓
I- I- I swear to God.
她之前在那 我看见她了
She was right there. I- I saw her.
她之前就在那
She was- she was- she was right there.
好了 来吧 该去洗手间了
Okay. Come on. Ifs bathroom time.
西恩娜 西恩娜
Sienna? Sienna?
好了 西恩娜 看着我 没事了 嘘 安静
Okay. Sienna, look at me. It's okay. Shh, shh, shh.
西恩娜 调整呼吸 没事的
Sienna, breathe. Breathe. Breathe. You're gonna be okay.
西恩娜
Sienna?
妈妈
Mom!
救命
Help me!
很抱歉 让你送我们
I'm sorry you had to leave.
没事
It's no problem.
你还好吗
You okay?
西恩娜 刚刚他妈的是怎么回事
Sienna, what the fuck was that back there?
我没事
Pm fine.
你他妈开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
不 你肯定有事儿
No! You're not fine.
你现在的样子肯定有事儿
You are so completely far from fine right now.
你刚刚简直被吓坏了
You're just totally freaked out.
哇 布鲁克 我也想知道为什么
Gee, Brooke. I wonder why.
这事别赖我
Don't blame this on me.
我现在跟你是一样是磕了药的 好吗
I'm on the same shit as you right now, okay?
我可没被吓坏
I'm not freaking out.
你们在说什么呢 磕什么药
What are we talking about here? What shit?
我在她酒里放了一点儿摇头丸
I put a pinch of molly in her drink.
这没什么
It was nothing.
- 外加阿普唑仑 - 什么
-Plus Xanax. - What?
我可没给你放阿普唑仑
I did not give you Xanax.
不 她已经吃了阿普唑仑 但没告诉我 懂了吗
No, she was already on Xanax, which I didn't know about, okay?
我们来把事情捋清楚
Let's make that perfectly fucking clear.
你他妈差点害死我
You could've fucking killed me.
我是为了你好
I was trying to do something nice for you.
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
你一直是这副病态女的样子
You're like Ms. Morbid all the time.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
送我回家就行
Just take me home.
西恩娜 不管刚才发生了什么那都不正常
Sienna, whatever happened back there was not normal.
好吗
Okay?
你可能患有脑动脉瘤
You could have had like a brain aneurysm,
或者脑癫痫之类的病
or seizure, or something.
如果再次发作呢
What if it happens again?
要送她去急诊室吗
Wanna take her to the emergency room?
我只想回家
I- I just- I just wanna go home.
送我回家就行
Just take me home.
如果是你妈妈打来的 别接
If that's your mother, do not answer it.
喂
Hello.
西恩娜 我有麻烦了
Sienna, I'm in trouble.
噢 你才意识到啊
Oh, you think?
妈妈把你干的好事告诉我了
Mommy told me what you did to her car,
你这小混蛋
you little asshole.
我是说至于这样吗
I mean, really?
不 我需要你帮忙
No. I need your help.
你得来接我
You have to come get me.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
怎么回事
What's wrong?
你在哪
Where are you?
我在旧嘉年华
I'm at the old carnival.
埃里克和肖恩把我丢在那了 就剩我一个了
Eric and Sean left me here. Fm all alone.
你怎么回事
What's wrong with you?
求你了 我真的好害怕
Please. I'm really scared.
我不知道该做什么 我不敢打给妈妈
I don't know what else to do. I can't call mommy.
好吧 呃 冷静
Okay. Um, all right. Calm down.
我会去接你的 好吗
I'll come get you, okay?
快来 我手机快没电了
Hurry, my phone is dying.
好 在大门口等我 好吗
All right. Just wait by the main entrance, okay?
乔纳森 乔纳森
Jonathan?Jonathan?]-
该死
Goddammit.
他耍你呢
He's bullshitting you.
不 他没有
No, he's not.
他就是在耍你
Yes, he is.
今天可是万圣节
Ifs Halloween.
你是想告诉我
Are you really telling me right now
你弟弟不会做这么古怪的事
that ifs beneath your brother to do something twisted
有失他的身份 得了吧 旧嘉年华
like this? Come on. The old carnival.
不 我听得出来他是不是撒谎 好吗
No. I--1 know when Jonathan's lying. Okay?
我能从他的声音里听出来
I--1 could hear it in his voice.
事情不太对劲
Something's-- something" wrong.
西恩娜 拜托
Sienna! Like, dude-
离这里没多远
It's only a few miles from here.
太蠢了
This is so stupid.
好极了 行吧 无所谓 我不在乎了
Great. Fine. Whatever. I dorYt care.
反正今天晚上也不会变得更糟了
It's not like this night can get any worse.
得 他人呢
Well, where is he?
我告诉他在门口等我
I told him to wait in front.
- 你弟弟多大了 - 十二岁
-How old's your brother? -12.
即便他人不在这儿
Even the fact that he*s out here right now
他也应该回你几句话
should be telling you something.
好像数年前一个小女孩
Didnft like a little girl get murdered out here
就是在这儿遇害的吧
a couple years ago?
我要去找他
I'm gonna go look for him.
什么
What?
西恩娜 回车上
Sienna? Get back in the car.
西恩娜
Sienna!
她疯了
She's crazy.
乔纳森
Jonathan!
也许我们应该和她一起去
Maybe we should go with her.
去你妈的 我向你保证
Fuck that. I guarantee you,
她弟弟会把她吓死的
her brother's just gonna scare the shit out of her.
他爸自杀以后
He's turned into a complete psycho
他就彻底疯了
ever since his father killed himself.
什么以后
Ever since what?
我没开玩笑
No joke.
他脑子里长了个大肿瘤
He had like this giant brain tumor
我也不知道 反正这个东西
that I don't know, it just made him do
让他做了一堆坏事
all this fucked-up shit.
他还出现幻觉了
And he was like seeing things.
变得很残暴
And he got really abusive towards the end.
尤其是对西恩娜
Especially towards Sienna.
有一天
And then one day,
他喝了一整瓶威士忌
he drank a whole bottle of Jack,
然后上了车径直撞向了
and he got in his car, and he drove straight
一个变压器
into one of those transformer things.
车着了火他被困在里面出不来
And the car caught fire, and he got trapped in the wreck.
最后活活被烧死了
And he burned to death.
你能从一英里外听到他的惨叫声
You could hear him screaming from a mile away.
我几小时前才认识你的朋友
Well, I've only known your friend for a few hours,
但这能解释很多事情
but that explains a lot.
没错
Yeah.
总的来说 我觉得她做得很好
All things considered, I think she's doing pretty well.
快回电话啊
Come on, answer me.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我在到处找你
I'm searching all over the place.
救命
Help.
乔纳森 能听到我说话吗
Jonathan, can you hear me?
我听不清
I can't--
听着
Listen.
我在旋转木马旁边等你好吗
I'm gonna wait for you by the merry-go-round, okay?
听到了吗
Did you hear what I said?
来旋转木马这里找我
Meet me at the merry-go-round.
喂
Hello?
记得回消息
Text me back.
什么东西
What is that?
提神的好东西
A little pick-me-up.
哇哦 杰夫 好吧
Wow, Jeff. Okay.
不要让西恩娜看到那玩意儿
Don't let Sienna see that shit.
我们在她回来之前吸完就好了
Well, well just have to do it before she comes back.
我不吸
Pm not doing that.
你试过吗
You ever try it?
试过一次 我不喜欢
Yeah. Once. I didn!t like it.
不可能 试试吧
Oh sure, impossible. Come on.
这玩意儿能让我们爽翻天
This will put us right back in the club.
妈的
Fuck.
相信我
Trust me.
好吧
Okay.
好 管他呢
All right. Fuck it.
好吧
okay.
味道好怪
That tastes weird.
乔纳森
Jonathan?
怎么了
Whafs wrong?
她到底去哪了
Where the hell is she?
管她去哪呢
Who cares?
等等
Wait.
听着 说真的
All right. Look, but, like, seriously,
她什么时候去的
what time did she leave?
- 谁在乎呢 - 好吧
-Well, who cares? -Okay.
我给她打个电话 好吗
Okay, I'm gonna call her really fast, okay?
很快的
Just really quick.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我要尿尿
I have to go pee-pee.
你想帮我吗
You wanna hold it?
好恶心 去吧
Ew. Leave.
嗨 我是西恩娜
Hi. It's Sienna.
有事请留言 我会回电话的
Leave a message, and I'll get back to you.
邮箱已满
The mailbox is full...
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你无法收到任何信息
...and cannot accept any messages at this time.
再见
Goodbye-
混蛋
Asshole!
第二次吓到你了
That's twice!
太有趣了
Oh, it's so funny.
没错 你太有趣了
Yeah, you're so funny.
你知道真正有趣的是什么吗
You know whafs actually really funny?
我看看 哦
Let me see here. Oh.
嘿 不要乱玩那个
Oh, hey. Don't fuck her up.
- 拜托了 - 哦
-Come on. -Oh.
- 你最好道个歉 - 对不起
-Oh, you better say sorry. -I'm sorry.
我不知道
And I don't really know
你能不能把这些从烟灰缸里吸出来
if you can snort this out of an ashtray.
肯定挺难的
It'd be kinda hard to snort out of.
对不起 对不起 我保证不会再这么做了
fm sorry! Tm sorry! I won't do it again, I promise.
你真的感到抱歉吗
Are you actually sorry?
好吧
Okay,fine.
你是个混蛋
But you're a jerk.
杰夫
Jeff?
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
不 不 不
No! No, no!
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
西恩娜
Sienna!
天呐
Oh, God!
西恩娜
Sienna!
我的天呐 我的天呐
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
乔纳森
Jonathan!
能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
有没有人 帮帮我
Somebody, please!
救救我
Help me!
西恩娜
Sienna!
救命
Help!
布鲁克
Brooke!
我的天呐 不要
Oh, my God! Noz please! No!
不要过来 求你了 离我远一点
Stay back. Stop. Please stop. Stay away from me!
不要过来
Don't, please!
等等 不要 求你了 不要
Wait, wait. No! Please, please stop! No!
不 不 不 不要 求你了
No, no, no, no! Stop it. Stop. No. Please!
不要过来 不要靠近我
No. Stay back. Don't…don't come near me.
求你了 不要 不要
Please don't. No, noz no!
布鲁克
Brooke!
Brooke.
乔纳森
Jonathan?
乔纳森 快跑
Jonathan, run!
快走
Come on.
这边走
This way.
西恩娜
Sienna.
你受伤了
You're hurt bad.
我没事 我没事 让我看看你
I'm all right. Tm all right. Let me... let me see you.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你说得对
You were right.
你说的都是对的
You were right about everything.
我也没有看错你
I was right about youz too.
什么
About what?
他们利用我把你引过来
They used me to get you here.
他们让你来到这里 是有原因的
They need you in this place for a reason.
你在说什么
What are you saying that?
爸爸看到了一些东西
Ifs what Daddy saw.
我觉得只有你可以阻止他
I think you're the only one who can stop him.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得离开这里
Well, we gotta find a way out of here.
好了 走吧
Okay, come on.
在这等我
Wait here.
乔纳森
Jonathan.
王八蛋
Sucker!
乔纳森
Jonathan-
西恩娜
Sienna!
西恩娜 西恩娜 醒醒
Sienna. Sienna, wake up.
醒醒 醒醒 你不要死啊
Stay with me. Stay with me! Please don't go.
西恩娜 不要离开我
Sienna. Please don't leave me.
西恩娜 宝贝 醒醒
Sienna. Baby, wake up.
妈妈
Mom?
亲爱的 没事了
Sweetie, ifs okay.
你现在安全了
You're safe.
妈妈
Mom.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
我以为我再也见不到你了
I thought I was never gonna see you again.
乔纳森告诉你的 对吗
Jonathan told you... didn't he?
什么
What?
西恩娜
Sienna!
离她远点 她不是妈妈
Get away from her! Thafs not Mommy!
乔纳森
Jonathan!
不 不
No! No!
不 不 你个混蛋
No! No, you tucker!
操你妈
Fuck you.
孩子们 说到奖品
Speaking of some prizes, kids,
我们今天请来一位特殊嘉宾
we have a very special guest with us today.
放我出去
Let me out!
西恩娜
Sienna!
Sienna.
你把他杀了
You got him.
都结束了 好吗
It's over now. Okay?
好的
Okay.
未完片尾彩蛋
请你告诉我这是南瓜香料
Please tell me this is pumpkin spice.
不可能
Not a chance in hell.
这是什么
What is this?
丧尸套餐 我老婆做的
Zombie platter. My wife made it.
好恶心
Thafs disgusting.
很有创意 但是很恶心
Creative, but disgusting.
不妨尝尝再说
I wouldn't say that before you try it.
还挺好吃的
It's pretty tasty.
不了 谢谢
Mm. No, thanks.
虽然那个脑子看上去很诱人
As appealing as that brain looks,
但我现在没有胃口
I don't really have the stomach for it right now.
一切都顺利吗
Everything okay?
我一整天都在照顾我们的名人病患
I've been tending to our celebrity patient all day.
情况很糟糕吗
Is that bad?
这么说吧 她的脸
Let's just say her face
看起来让人很没食欲
doesn't stimulate one's appetite.
- 她怎么样 - 脾气很好
-Whafs she like? -Tame.
挺配合的
Pretty cooperative actually.
很难想象她把那个女人肢解的样子
Ifs kind of hard to imagine she ripped that woman to pieces.
给我一个眼球
Pass me one of those eyeballs.
上面放点脑冻
And, uh, put some of that brain jelly on it, too.
洛拉 不要放这么少 对了 这就对了
And, Lola, don't be stingy. Oh. There it is. There you go.
再来一点
Little more.
谢谢你 我明天开始节食
Thank you. Diet starts tomorrow, so...
什么歌
What is that?
你在唱什么歌
That song you're singing, what is it?
我也不知道
I have no idea actually.
维多利亚唱这首歌唱了一整天了
Victoria's been singing it all day.
我脑袋里一直在循环这首歌
I can't get it out of my head.
你就是个婊子
You fucking cunt!
婊子
Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!
天呐
Oh, God.